qbrick.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy - Qbrick

Qbrick AB (”us”, ”we”, or ”our”) operates qbrick.com & ucast.se (the ”Sites”) including subdomains. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site(s).

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site(s). By using the Site(s), you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

###  **Information Collection and Use**

While using our Site(s), we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (”Personal Information”).

###  **Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site(s) (”Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (”IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site(s) that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services for example analytics services that collect, monitor and analyze this.

###  **Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information.

###  **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Like many sites, we use ”cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site(s).

###  **Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

###  **Your data rights as a user**

As a user you have the right to the following actions in relation to your personal records. You have the right to:

  * Withdraw all personal records stored about you

  * Adjust any personal records stored about you

  * To delete any personal records stored about you

  * Limit the handling of any personal records stored about you

  * Object against a certain type of handling of your personal records

  * Export your personal records to another provider

In order for you to take use of any of the actions above, please contact us through either our general support services or send us an email at support@qbrick.com

###  **Where can I report potential misuse of my personal records**

Datainspektionen is the supervisory authority to which you can report any form of misuse of your personal records. You can find the necessary contact details below.

 **Website:**  www.datainspektionen.se  
 **Telephone number:**  08-657 61 00  
 **Email:**  [datainspektionen@datainspektionen.se](mailto:datainspektionen@datainspektionen.se)  
 **Fax:**  08-652 86 52

###  **Future changes to our policy**

We reserve the right to modify or update this policy in order to be fully transparent with any changes or updates to our services as well as to reflect to any new changes made to the current data protection regulations. Make sure to periodically review this page in order to take part of the latest version.   

###  **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us below.

Färögatan 33 SE 164 41 Kista  
Phone: +46 8 459 90 00

Contact our customer service, at +46 8 459 90 00 or through support@qbrick.com, if you have any questions regarding data security or your personal records.
